I will have someone
use the best medicine for your wound.
The girl and I will take our leave first.
Uncle,
Bai Ze just saved me.
Why are you so cold to him?
I see.
It's because of Feng Qingwu, right?
She is your fiancée.
But Bai Ze only knocked her out.
You...
Listen to me, girl.
Stay away from that boy
from Yungong Pavilion from now on.
Where is this?
Wu Hall.
From now on,
you can't go anywhere.
As for the reason,
I think you should know.
What do you mean?
Just for that wild girl?
Attacking the Sect Leader's wife.
Locking you up
is already the Sect Leader showing mercy.
Ye Qifeng,
you seem to have forgotten
what I am best at.
Isn't this Lady Feng Qingwu
who hurt me last night?
Are you planning to apologize to me?
I came to you to discuss
an important matter.
I can tell Mr. Bai likes A Kong very much.
Why don't we join forces
so we can each get the one we love?
What a good proposal.
Too bad I'm not interested.
Ah!
Feng Qingwu,
escaping without permission
adds to your crimes.
By the Sect Leader's order,
I will escort you to Mount Qilin.
If you dare to escape again,
you will be punished by the sect rules.
Ye Qifeng,
hundreds of years of our friendship,
and all I get is punishment
by the sect rules?
This is already out of respect
for our hundreds of years
of friendship and Senior Feng.
Aren't you afraid
I'll detonate the puppet?
What puppet?
Who is your puppet?
Sister, will you stay in Yan Sect
this time you come back?
Yes, I will stay to cure Uncle.
Great!
Qiongqi,
why are you here?
You...
Oh no,
his state is the same as
when he went berserk before.
If I guess correctly,
the puppet Feng Qingwu mentioned should be
Qiongqi.
Qiongqi, why are you here?
I think I just...
killed someone.
Bai, hold on.
Why did you block in front of me just now?
Because I like you, Sister.
You look very much like her.
Every time I see you, I think of her.
Her?
I can't remember her face
and voice clearly anymore.
But I just feel you two are very alike.
The first time I saw you,
I liked you in my heart.
Yes,
I like you too, Bai.
Then don't marry Uncle Zhi,
marry me, okay?
Uncle Zhi is the old monster.
His original name was Qi Zhezhi.
But this name hasn't been used
for hundreds of years.
What a touching display of affection.
Let me help you out
and send you both to hell.
Prepare to die!
I think you're the one
who should prepare to die.
Lord Bai,
I'll send you back right away.
"Send us to hell," huh?
"Prepare to die," huh?
Who is that kicking Hei Wuya so hard?